What were you thinking?
The only way people
won't suspect anything,
even if they recognize me,
is to show them I'm on vacation.
I spoke with Joey.
He's with Andrew.
They said they're
following a lead.
Let's just follow Andrew.
We can help them too.
Instead of getting closer,
I'll keep my distance.
I'll just go home
to the province.
I might not be able to take care
of this foundation for now.
Mom lost her caregiver.
Ma'am, if you can't find anyone,
I can help.
If you agree,
it won't just be me helping you,
you'll be helping me too.
Sir, the package was delivered
to Delgado.
Hopefully that helps
his mission.
Thank you, Chief.
Whose is it?
The guy in red,
we saw him in the other room.
He called Delilah "boss."
You're my ticket
to get close to Delilah.
And if it's any help,
we confirmed Delilah is here.
She's just in the room
next to us.
I'm Madam Delilah.
I'm Joey.
We have camping areas.
Don't worry,
I'll have it prepared.
Too bad I have plans later.
Castro said someone
asked about Berdugo.
To avoid problems, I'll attend
the meeting with Delilah.
She left, but I heard
she'll be back tonight.
This is our chance.
No one's at the villa.
We can go in and find a clue.
- Can you open that?
- Of course.
Hello? I'm done cleaning.
I'm on my way there.
[OBB]
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, I'm on my way.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Boss, if you want, I'll get it
so you won't get tired.
What do you need to get?
My dear,
I trust you but...
I don't trust you enough
to give you personally
the combination of my safe.
I'll come back myself.
Boys, let's go.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Just give it to Joey.
He might pass by.
Okay.
Are you sure about leaving?
What about your work
with your uncle here?
It's fine. I already told him.
I'm needed back home,
unlike here.
What? Did I hear that right?
You're leaving,
you're teasing me again.
- Teasing?
- You're leaving
because Joey has forgotten you,
right?
What? Admit it.
- Come on.
- Admit it.
Fine, I need to go.
Take care here.
Thank you so much.
All right, friend.
Take care too.
-Take care, friend.
-Take care.
- Bye.
- Hey! You're really leaving?
My god! It's okay.
Okay.
Why are you so red?
Are you okay?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought we'd get caught.
Let's go!
Okay.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You know what? Stay here.
Okay? Wait for me.
- I'll look for...
- You're leaving me here?
- Yes.
- Really?
Andrew!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- All right. You two stay there.
- All right, Boss.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew!
Andrew, let me in.
You're starting to annoy me.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey! Joey, there's a safe here.
Do you know the combination?
How would I know?
Try 1-2-3-4.
1-2-3. I already tried that.
Still nothing.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why won't you let me in?
I might find a clue!
Andrew, let's go!
Someone might see us here!
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew, someone might come!
Hurry up!
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew...
Andrew!
Joey?
What are you doing there?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
It hurts!
Awww!
- Miss!
- Ouch!
What happened to you?
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not!
What happened
to you, ma'am?
"Ma'am"?
I'm not that old.
I slipped!
Because no one cleaned!
Sorry, Miss...
Zoey.
Wait. Are you a guest here?
Can you come with me to
see the resort manager?
I'll file a complaint.
I'll vlog about what
happened to me!
Miss Zoey, Francis,
owner of the resort.
You're right, it's our fault.
Please accept our apology.
So you're the owner?
Miss Zoey, maybe we can talk...
so we can fix this?
If you want, your stay here
will be free of charge.
Is that your best offer?
FYI,
I can pay for my accommodation
in this cheap resort.
Miss Zoey, you're right.
Our resort is very simple.
But I'm sure you haven't tried
our amenities.
We're very proud
of our nature experiences
which you can try out.
So, can I offer...
dinner by the campsite?
Wait, so...
just me?
You won't even join me?
Don't worry, Miss Zoey. I'll
join you.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why are you standing outside
my room?
I'm looking for my boyfriend.
You know what? When I see him,
he'll have to deal with me.
I've had it with him.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Lover's quarrel.
What happened?
It seems that guy forgot
he's here with someone.
I just took a nap,
then he disappeared!
Annoying, right?
That's so sweet.
You're so in love you
don't want to be apart.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUDS]
Look.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Check everywhere!
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Check inside!
Maybe it was just the wind?
It can't be.
Look, all the doors and windows
are closed.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What? Did you see anything?
Ma'am, there was nothing.
Well, I guess you're right,
dear.
Maybe it was just the wind.
Oh, are you okay?
You look scared.
It's because of what sir
was holding.
I'm not used to guns.
They're scary.
Ah, is that so?
Hey, put that away.
You're scaring my neighbor.
Sorry about that, dear.
You know, these dayls,
you can't trust anyone.
Are you sure you're okay?
Sorry again for what you saw.
It's fine.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Babe!
What are you doing here?
Where were you?
I've been looking for you.
I even called your mom
to let her know that
we're having fun and we're safe.
That's so sweet.
Ma'am Delilah.
I'm Andrew.
You look familiar.
Anyway, make up already,
you two.
Don't waste your stay
at my resort
over a small misunderstanding.
Thank you, Aunt Delilah.
- Thank you.
- Aunt?
Nobody has called
me that before.
I kind of like it.
[GROANS]
You know what?
I feel so much better now.
Thank you.
- Did the pain subside?
- Yes, yes, thanks.
So maybe we're now absolved
from that incident you had?
You might post bad reviews
about our hotel on social media.
Don't worry.
I'm not that kind of person.
I won't do that.
Don't be afraid, okay?
Really?
Thank you then.
We just want our resort
to stay quiet.
Because if this gets posted
online and goes viral,
it'll draw attention here.
Then our resort
will become noisy.
Even if you don't have
that many customers?
What's important is the privacy
of our guests.
Why?
Do you have famous guests here?
Powerful people?
Or maybe criminal masterminds
are hiding here?
Ouch...
You're so dramatic.
But it's your fault.
You left me, remember?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
But you know,
if you weren't outside earlier,
I would've been caught.
So...
thank you.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Still.
You should've brought me inside.
If I were there,
we might've found a clue.
Never mind.
We still have a chance.
Okay? Come on, I'm sorry.
Don't be mad anymore.
[GROANS]
- You even pressed harder.
- Stop moving.
Thank you.
By the way, you actually did...
well earlier.
Really?
Yes.
If not for your delaying
tactics,
I would've been caught.
And even though I know
you're annoyed with me,
you didn't abandon me.
Of course.
It's not like I'd want anything
bad to happen to my boyfriend.
[HEART POUNDING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES]
Just kidding!
Just kidding! Come on!
I'm just like this.
Hey, don't get annoyed with me,
okay? I'm just like this.
This is just me.
You might suddenly ditch me
at our dinner.
7 PM, I'll pick you up.
It's a date.
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Anyway, I'll go ahead.
- All right.
- So, I'll see you?
- 7 PM.
- Yeah. Bye!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
We should stick
with our characters.
Of course, we're pretending to
be boyfriend and girlfriend.
So, we have to be consistent.
No one should catch us,
no one should suspect anything.
Right.
You have a point.
Maybe we shouldn't just
pretend in front of Delilah.
We should pretend in
front of everyone.
Because think about it,
we almost got caught earlier.
Who knows? Next time, Delilah
might ask questions.
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
So...
what do we do?
Then we have to convince
everyone that...
we really are together.
I know. I have an idea.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
To the right.
[WHOOSHING]
90 degrees, right.
Can you still do it? Okay.
Step forward.
[WHOOSHING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[APPLAUDING]
You two act so well.
I would believe
you're really a couple.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Zoey, I thought you don't want
your cover blown.
Why are you here?
Didn't you say we'd share info?
Well, I just want
to let you know
I have a date with Francis
tonight.
This is my chance to
get closer to Delilah's circle.
Great.
Well, I guess that's good.
Good for you.
But be careful,
just looking at Francis,
I already don't trust him.
You're worried about me,
just like before.
[ZOEY CHUCKLES]
I'm just saying that he might
be dangerous for you.
But good luck on your date.
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey!
Damn you, Andrew.
This doesn't feel like
pretending anymore.
-You stink already.
-Come on, let's go. Let's go.
- No! Take a bath.
- Go, go, go!
[SPLASHES]
[DREAMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SPLASHING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
I know we're losing patrons
because the stocks of our drugs
are running out
since Godfather disappeared.
But...
the good news
is we have a new supplier.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN COCKS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Why did you really come home,
brother?
There's something
I just want to forget.
Whatever it is, whoever it is,
I'll help you forget.
What's your plan now?
Maybe I'll just talk
to Sir Tomas.
Do not deal with him.
Where's your mother?
Dad, sorry,
but I haven't gone home yet.
Joey?
Who's that? Is that Andrew?
You can't join the operation.
Civilians aren't allowed.
This is a major operation.
Target site, Nature Resort
owned by Francis Toledo.
And we're working
with the theory
that they have a deal
with Berdugo.
Tell everyone.
Take your positions.
- Copy, Sir.
- Let's start the transaction.
I don't want to waste time.
Bravo, secure exit.
Andrew, follow me.
- [GUN FIRING]
- Could those be the people
looking for you?
Just a skirmish, Ma'am.
I'll handle it.
Better be careful.
He might catch up with you.